<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.xwaylandvideobridge.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Xwayland Video Bridge</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Pont de vídeo de l'Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pont de vídeo d'XWayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Xwayland video-bridge</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Interface de Vídeo para o Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Xwayland Video Köprüsü</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Відеомісток Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxXwayland Video Bridgexx</name>
  <summary>Offer XDG Desktop Portals screencast streams to X11 apps</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Ofereix fluxos de vídeo de captura de pantalla dels «XDG Desktop Portals» a les aplicacions X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Oferix fluxos de vídeo de captura de pantalla dels «XDG Desktop Portals» a les aplicacions X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">XDG schermfilmstreams van bureaubladportalen bieden aan X11 toepassingen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Disponibiliza transmissões do XDG Desktop Portals para as aplicações de X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">X11 uygulamalarına XDG Masaüstü Portalları ekran yayını akışları sun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Надає змогу порталам стільниці XDG транслювати потоки даних до програм X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxOffer XDG Desktop Portals screencast streams to X11 appsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Many X11 apps will be using X11 mechanisms to share the contents of other applications and displays. In recent years we have created XDG Desktop Portals as the mechanism to provide this functionality and it's what we expect apps to be using it. This application will provide the streams available to the XDG Desktop Portals to your legacy X11 apps that have not adopted the new system.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Moltes aplicacions X11 estaran utilitzant els mecanismes X11 per a compartir el contingut d'altres aplicacions i pantalles. En els darrers anys hem creat els «XDG Desktop Portals» com un mecanisme de proporcionar aquesta funcionalitat i és el que esperem que les aplicacions facin servir. Aquesta aplicació proporcionarà els fluxos disponibles per als «XDG Desktop Portals» a les vostres aplicacions X11 antigues que encara no hagin adoptat el sistema nou.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Moltes aplicacions X11 estaran utilitzant els mecanismes X11 per a compartir el contingut d'altres aplicacions i pantalles. En els darrers anys hem creat els «XDG Desktop Portals» com un mecanisme de proporcionar esta característica i és el que esperem que les aplicacions facen servir. Esta aplicació proporcionarà els fluxos disponibles per als «XDG Desktop Portals» a les vostres aplicacions X11 antigues que encara no hagen adoptat el sistema nou.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Veel X11 toepassingen zullen X11-mechanismen gebruiken om de inhoud van andere toepassen en schermen te delen. In recente jaren hebben we XDG bureaubladportalen als het mechanisme gebruikt om deze functionaliteit te leveren en het is wat we verwachten dat toepassingen het gebruiken. Deze toepassing zal de streams beschikbaar aan de XDG bureaubladportalen leveren aan uw oudere X11-toepassingen die niet aan het nieuwe systeem zijn aangepast.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Muitas das aplicações do X11 irão usar mecanismos do X11 para partilhar os conteúdos de outras aplicações e ecrãs. Recentemente, criámos o XDG Desktop Portals como mecanismo para oferecer esta funcionalidade, e é o que esperamos que as aplicações comecem a usar. Esta aplicação irá fornecer as transmissões disponíveis do XDG Desktop Portals às suas aplicações antigas do X11 que ainda não tenham adoptado o novo sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Birçok X11 uygulaması, diğer uygulamaların ve ekranların içeriklerini paylaşmak için X11 mekanizmalarını kullanır. Son yıllarda, bu işlevselliği sağlamak için mekanizma olarak XDG Masaüstü Portalları'nı oluşturduk ve uygulamaların bunu kullanmasını bekliyoruz. Bu uygulama, XDG Masaüstü Portalları'nda var olan akışları, yeni sistemi benimsememiş eski X11 uygulamalarınıza sağlayacaktır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Багато програм X11 використовують механізми X11 для оприлюднення даних інших програм та дисплеїв. Протягом останніх років ми створили портали стільниць XDG як механізм надання цих функціональних можливостей, і саме ними мають користуватися програми. Ця програма надає доступ до потоків даних порталів XDG ваших застарілим програмам X11, які не адаптовано до нової системи.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMany X11 apps will be using X11 mechanisms to share the contents of other applications and displays. In recent years we have created XDG Desktop Portals as the mechanism to provide this functionality and it's what we expect apps to be using it. This application will provide the streams available to the XDG Desktop Portals to your legacy X11 apps that have not adopted the new system.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/system/xwaylandvideobridge</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/system/xwaylandvideobridge</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations</url>
  <provides>
    <binary>xwaylandvideobridge</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
