<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.xwaylandvideobridge.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Xwayland Video Bridge</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Pont de vídeo de l'Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pont de vídeo d'XWayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Propojení videa Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Xwayland-Video-Brücke</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Xwayland Video Bridge</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Pasarela de vídeo Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Xwayland bideo zubia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Pont vidéo XWayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Xwayland-ის ვიდეოხიდი</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Xwayland video-bridge</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Interface de Vídeo para o Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Xwayland video most</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Xwayland Video Bridge</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Xwayland Video Köprüsü</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Відеомісток Xwayland</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxXwayland Video Bridgexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Xwayland 视频桥接程序</name>
  <summary>Offer XDG Desktop Portals screencast streams to X11 apps</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Ofereix fluxos de vídeo de captura de pantalla dels «XDG Desktop Portals» a les aplicacions X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Oferix fluxos de vídeo de captura de pantalla dels «XDG Desktop Portals» a les aplicacions X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Offer XDG Desktop Portals screencast streams to X11 apps</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ofrecer emisiones de vídeo de los portales de escritorio XDG a las aplicaciones de X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Eskaini XDG mahaigain atarien pantaila-grabazio korronteak X11 aplikazioei</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Proposer des flux de diffusion d’écrans pour des portails e bureaux « XDG » vers les applications sous X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">X11-ის აპებისთვის XDG Desktop Portals-ის screencast ნაკადების შეთავაზება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">XDG schermfilmstreams van bureaubladportalen bieden aan X11 toepassingen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Disponibiliza transmissões do XDG Desktop Portals para as aplicações de X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Nudi portalom namizja XDG zaslonske tokove aplikacijam X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">X11 uygulamalarına XDG Masaüstü Portalları ekran yayını akışları sun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Надає змогу порталам стільниці XDG транслювати потоки даних до програм X11</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxOffer XDG Desktop Portals screencast streams to X11 appsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">将 XDG 桌面门户投屏视频流提供给 X11 应用程序</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Many X11 apps will be using X11 mechanisms to share the contents of other applications and displays. In recent years we have created XDG Desktop Portals as the mechanism to provide this functionality and it's what we expect apps to be using it. This application will provide the streams available to the XDG Desktop Portals to your legacy X11 apps that have not adopted the new system.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Moltes aplicacions X11 estaran utilitzant els mecanismes X11 per a compartir el contingut d'altres aplicacions i pantalles. En els darrers anys hem creat els «XDG Desktop Portals» com un mecanisme de proporcionar aquesta funcionalitat i és el que esperem que les aplicacions facin servir. Aquesta aplicació proporcionarà els fluxos disponibles per als «XDG Desktop Portals» a les vostres aplicacions X11 antigues que encara no hagin adoptat el sistema nou.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Moltes aplicacions X11 estaran utilitzant els mecanismes X11 per a compartir el contingut d'altres aplicacions i pantalles. En els darrers anys hem creat els «XDG Desktop Portals» com un mecanisme de proporcionar esta característica i és el que esperem que les aplicacions facen servir. Esta aplicació proporcionarà els fluxos disponibles per als «XDG Desktop Portals» a les vostres aplicacions X11 antigues que encara no hagen adoptat el sistema nou.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Many X11 apps will be using X11 mechanisms to share the contents of other applications and displays. In recent years we have created XDG Desktop Portals as the mechanism to provide this functionality and it's what we expect apps to be using it. This application will provide the streams available to the XDG Desktop Portals to your legacy X11 apps that have not adopted the new system.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Muchas aplicaciones de X11 usarán mecanismos de X11 para compartir el contenido de otras aplicaciones y pantallas. En los últimos años, hemos creado los portales de escritorio XDG como el mecanismo para proporcionar esta funcionalidad y es lo que esperamos que usen las aplicaciones. Esta aplicación proporcionará las transmisiones disponibles para los portales de escritorio XDG a las aplicaciones X11 heredadas que no han adoptado el nuevo sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">X11 aplikazio askok X11 mekanismoak erabiliko dituzte beste aplikazio eta bistaratzaile batzuen edukia partekatzeko. Azken urteetan XDG mahaigaineko atariak sortu ditugu funtzionalitate hori emateko mekanismo gisa, eta espero dugu aplikazioek haiek erabiltzea. Aplikazio horrek XDG mahaigaineko atarietarako eskuragarri dauden korronteak emango dizkie sistema berria hartu ez duten X11 ondare aplikazioei.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">De nombreuses applications fonctionnant sous X11 utiliseront les mécanismes sous X11 pour partager le contenu d’autres applications et affichages. Ces dernières années, les portails de bureaux « XDG » ont été créés comme le mécanisme pour fournir cette fonctionnalité. Ce mécanisme devrait être utilisé dans l'avenir par les applications. Il fournira les flux disponibles pour les portails de bureau « XDG » à vos anciennes applications sous X11 sans qu'elles aient besoin d'adopter ce nouveau mécanisme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">X11-ის ბევრი აპი იყენებს X11-ის მექანიზმს სხვადასხვა მონაცემების სხვა პროგრამებისთვის გასაზიარებლად. ბოლო წლებში ჩვენ შევქმენით XDG Desktop Portals, როგორც მექანიზმი, რათა ეს ფუნქციონალი მოგვეწოდებინა და მოველით, რომ აპები მას გამოიყენებენ. ეს აპლიკაცია XDG Desktop Portals-სთვის ხელმისაწვდომ ნაკადებს თქვენს მოძველებულ X11-ის აპებს გაუზიარებს, რითიც ისინი ახალ ფუნქციონალს გამოიყენებენ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Veel X11 toepassingen zullen X11-mechanismen gebruiken om de inhoud van andere toepassen en schermen te delen. In recente jaren hebben we XDG bureaubladportalen als het mechanisme gebruikt om deze functionaliteit te leveren en het is wat we verwachten dat toepassingen het gebruiken. Deze toepassing zal de streams beschikbaar aan de XDG bureaubladportalen leveren aan uw oudere X11-toepassingen die niet aan het nieuwe systeem zijn aangepast.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Muitas das aplicações do X11 irão usar mecanismos do X11 para partilhar os conteúdos de outras aplicações e ecrãs. Recentemente, criámos o XDG Desktop Portals como mecanismo para oferecer esta funcionalidade, e é o que esperamos que as aplicações comecem a usar. Esta aplicação irá fornecer as transmissões disponíveis do XDG Desktop Portals às suas aplicações antigas do X11 que ainda não tenham adoptado o novo sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Številne aplikacije X11 bodo uporabljale mehanizme X11 za skupno rabo vsebin drugih aplikacij in prikazov. V zadnjih letih smo ustvarili portale namizja XDG Portali kot mehanizem za zagotavljanje te funkcionalnosti in pričakujemo, da ga bodo aplikacije tudi uporabljale. Ta aplikacija bo zagotovila tokove na voljo na portalih namizja  XDG za vaše podedovane aplikacije X11, ki se še niso prilagodile na novi sistem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Birçok X11 uygulaması, diğer uygulamaların ve ekranların içeriklerini paylaşmak için X11 mekanizmalarını kullanır. Son yıllarda, bu işlevselliği sağlamak için mekanizma olarak XDG Masaüstü Portalları'nı oluşturduk ve uygulamaların bunu kullanmasını bekliyoruz. Bu uygulama, XDG Masaüstü Portalları'nda var olan akışları, yeni sistemi benimsememiş eski X11 uygulamalarınıza sağlayacaktır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Багато програм X11 використовують механізми X11 для оприлюднення даних інших програм та дисплеїв. Протягом останніх років ми створили портали стільниць XDG як механізм надання цих функціональних можливостей, і саме ними мають користуватися програми. Ця програма надає доступ до потоків даних порталів XDG ваших застарілим програмам X11, які не адаптовано до нової системи.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMany X11 apps will be using X11 mechanisms to share the contents of other applications and displays. In recent years we have created XDG Desktop Portals as the mechanism to provide this functionality and it's what we expect apps to be using it. This application will provide the streams available to the XDG Desktop Portals to your legacy X11 apps that have not adopted the new system.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">许多 X11 应用程序会使用 X11 的机制来分享其他应用程序和显示器中的内容。为了取代上述机制并提供相同的功能，我们开发了 XDG 桌面门户程序，并默认应用程序会使用它。此应用程序用于将 XDG 桌面门户程序中的可用视频流提供给尚未适配新系统的旧式 X11 应用程序。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/system/xwaylandvideobridge</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/system/xwaylandvideobridge</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations</url>
  <provides>
    <binary>xwaylandvideobridge</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
